Hello friends, my name is Ashwini Kumar
and brother I work in IIC Bank, so
brother, as you can see this strap,
you have this ID card around my neck, so
brother, I have just come from the office
and brother, I have started making videos here just for you, let me get it out
quickly, let me
make a video for you as quickly as possible
because brother, this is the first time, many
people have commented that brother,
bring a video on this topic, bring a video on this topic,
so brother, today the video has come, do
watch the video till the end, what
people do first is that they will watch it for one to two minutes
and then immediately back the video, brother,
first see what information has been given,
what has been said, you should apply it once,
okay, you see
how much effort I am putting in for you, okay and
what do you do, there is a subscription, it is free, it is
free of cost, if
you do not subscribe to that also, then brother,
please you must watch the video till the end,
I will tell you the rest of the details
and brother, as friends, you
You must have seen in the title and thumbnail
that today's video is going to be here,
I have brought today's video for you,
brother, it is on this topic that brother,
if you go for an interview, then brother, how
can you give the interview here,
what questions are going to come in the interview, I have
given the interview in II Bank, I have been
selected here, what questions were asked to me,
how did I crack my interview
and brother, if you are a fresher and
brother, if you are an experience and you are also going to
give an interview in a bank somewhere
or you are preparing for the interview, then
brother, how can you give it, what
questions can be asked, about those questions,
friends, today's video is going to be a
topic here, brother, friends, I have a
special video for you, the top 10 questions that are
asked here, which are asked
in the interview,
go to any interview, give
100% marks there  Questions will definitely be asked,
you should prepare these questions, you
can do it in Hindi also, there is no problem in it,
you just have to do it in English,
whatever your introduction is,
friends, you have to give it in English only
because brother, you are going to a bank, so
brother, English becomes
mandatory here, by the way friends, you
can answer any other questions that will be asked of you in Hindi, there is no
problem in it, brother, whatever
questions there are, I have brought the top 10 questions for you,
how I have
given the interview here and brother, I am
selected in ICICI Bank, you must know
and brother, how I have cracked my interview here,
what questions were asked
from me, friends, I am going to
tell you the complete details here in today's video,
so you have to do only one thing, you
must watch the video till the end, if you like the video then
definitely give it a like,
friends, if you are new to this channel then also
you must subscribe to the channel
because brother, here  You keep getting such content, without wasting
time, let's
start the video, let's talk
friends about the interview here, brother, the
first question you are going to have here,
brother, I will take out my mobile
and guide you step by step,
okay brother, I have turned on the
screen recording of my mobile and brother, the
screen recording of my mobile is done,
so brother, the
first question here is going to be tell me about
yourself, okay, you have to go
to any interview, it is not that you will go
only in the banking sector,
you have to go to any interview, the first question
you are going to have here is going to be tell
me about
yourself, okay, if you answer this question
very well, then
half
your interview ends here and this question of yours,
brother, this
question will be asked to you everywhere and
in this question you have to
tell your classification which is within you  You have to
tell about your skills, you have to
tell about your experience, if you
are a fresher, what skills have you learned,
when did you do your schooling, when did you do your graduation, you have to disclose
all the information about yourself
here, that too brother, get
a good introduction in English from GPT
written here and
practice on your own, the more you practice, the less
nervous you will feel
whenever you have your first interview,
what happens the first time is that brother,
all the candidates feel nervous here,
which I also used to feel, but now it does not happen
because brother, I have
given a lot of interviews, I have experience, let me
sit in any interview,
now there is not going to be any problem for
me, it is fine, the second question comes, why do you want to work
from a private bank,
why do you want to work in a private bank, the most important thing is that
brother, if you are a
fresher here, you want to come into the banking sector, then
brother, you will definitely be asked  That
brother, why do you want to do it, brother, the
answer to this is going to be given in simple language
that what all do you have to give,
what do you have to tell brother, keeping those things in
mind brother, you
can also get it written through chat.JPT or you can also ask someone
or friends, the link is given below,
you will also get my question number
easily and brother, here your third question is going to be the third question, the
third question I will
tell you is how do you handle pressure
and tight deadlines, okay, you will be asked
that if you are under pressure, brother,
how will you handle it, these questions that I am
telling you brother have been
asked to me directly, okay, I am
not telling you the questions just like that, I will tell you
that brother, the questions have already been asked to me, that is why
I am telling you,
I have just written down
what all you have to tell you, after that the
fifth question which comes is what is your
understanding of wealth management,
how will you
handle your management  What are your
skills and how will you manage them related to them, in
this way friends,
you have to make your answer and
tell it, brother you can write it on a pen or coffee pen, if you
want you can tell Chat GPT
that brother what are the top 10
interview questions, that too
of the banking sector, rest of the friends, let me
tell you an update, brother, if you want a job here in
any pen in India, anywhere, the
link is given below, the
link is given, you can connect here,
rest of the brother, the eighth question here is going to be tell
me about time, your date
and resolve your confirmation and work, okay,
how will you manage your time and
brother, how will you resolve it and brother, the
famous question which is going to be here,
you can go to any banking sector,
this is the most famous question of all, what are your
strengths and work, friends,
you have to tell this here in a positive manner,
brother, whatever your
Brother, you have to tell them in a positive manner about your strength and nature. You will get
YouTube videos etc. You should
watch them once. After that, friends,
you should prepare here for your first interview.
By the way, friends,
I told you how I
gave the interview for the first time. Friends,
I was also asked the same questions for which
I had prepared well. There is no
problem at all.
Friends, you will not be asked
how much English you know, how to do it,
what to do. If you know a little
English, you should give your introduction
here in English properly.
Whatever English you know, it may be broken but it should be
good. You should repeat it and memorize the
introduction 20 times, 50 times,
100 times. You have to give your introduction
in English only. If you
want to work in the banking sector, then
talk about the rest of the questions in Hindi. There is
no problem if you are a
fresher, then brother, whatever entry level
you get, brother, you can apply here in the banking
sector.  Enter in it, after that
as you gain experience,
you will get to know more about the packing sector, so
brother, there is no problem in it,
then you will definitely get to know, for freshers
friends, let me tell you that whatever
your introduction is, prepare it 100% well, brother, the
same thing happened with me,
I have prepared very well
and brother, brother, when I went there, brother, brother, there were two to
three people sitting there and brother, I gave the
interview there,
they asked different questions, but my English is
not that strong, the rest is fine, it is quite good, there is no
problem
brother, brother, I interacted with them live to
live and that is, face to face and then
they interviewed me, then they
took the third round, there were two to three rounds,
after that I got selected here
in ICICI Bank, okay and it takes 10 to 15 days,
it is not that you go today and get
your call back today itself  The pickle is that you have been selected
or you get the documentation and
verification done, this is that, it is not like that, it can take
20 to 25 days, it can
also take a month and it will depend on
how tough the process of the bank is, that is,
how fast the process is, friends, I have made today
's video only to tell you
that brother, how can you prepare for the interview, I have
told you how I gave it, you have to give your
best introduction, you have to memorize 10 to 15
questions here, there is no problem,
get them written by Chat GPT,
you will be 100% selected, brother, if you
crack the interview well then
go for formals, you should know
how people live in the banking sector, how they do
not work, how they live, they are formals, they are
very formal,
what happens is that brother, they leave just like you can see,
brother, this will not work, it will
not work in the banking sector, you will
work in a bank, you should be professional,
you should become professional  It will be necessary, that is
why I am telling you that
you should go after building your personality in a good way, get your
Balbal and the same D etc. cleared, that is,
whatever you do, you have to go after being
clean, you should feel
that you are working in a bank, okay,
you should give your best introduction, conduct your
interview properly, answer whatever is asked of you, do
not tell anything extra about yourself, so
brother, by doing this in this way, friends, you
can correct the interview easily, brother,
I have told you whatever was my
experience, I have told you, so
brother, this was today's video, I hope
you liked this video very much, if you liked the video then
like it, if
you have not subscribed to this channel yet, then
brother, quickly go and subscribe to this channel, we will meet
next time and
till then take care bye